BGM
Well, here we are at Apkami. This time with Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory,
and Ichika Arisawa of Chus Chus.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Onoda, am currently touring with Tsubaki Factory for our spring concert.
This is the first and last concert tour for the 12 of us, since a new member joined the group and this is the last tour for Sora Arai no Maki-chan.
This is the first and last concert tour for 12 members,
The three new members were really quick to learn,
But the three new members were really quick to learn, even though there were so many Y values and so on,
I can't remember them,
I thought they must have practiced a lot at home,
I think they must be practicing a lot at home. We also teach each other detailed dance moves together,
When we teach each other detailed dance moves, they learn them quickly and respond to them instantly,
We also gave each other advice on how we should do things.
They gave each other advice on how to do things.
It was a rehearsal for the tour where I could really feel the growth.
This will be the last concert that I will be spending with Kisara Niinuma, and we will be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the last time.
We are going to perform at Nippon Budokan at the end of the tour.
We will be performing at the Nippon Budokan for the last time, and I would like to continue to work hard toward that concert tour.
As for Juice Juice, Mio Kawashima will be back from the spring tour.
Mio Kawashima will be back from the spring tour.
We are all united in our efforts.
We are working very hard right now.
As for me, Arisawa...
Mr. Uemura's last tour
I'm currently touring with Mr. Uemura.
Among all the tours
For example, during the rehearsals, I had a dance teacher who taught me the last original member's choreography and singing style of Juice Juice.
You are the person who knows the most about JuiceJuice's choreography and how to sing, aren't you?
That's right.
So when I heard that I should absorb all of that so that JuiceJuice can go on for a long time, I thought, "I'm going to miss you, Uemura-san.
I realized that Mr. Uemura was going to leave us, and I've been feeling that way a lot lately.
There are many moments when I really feel that Tsubaki Factory also has graduating members of JuiceJuice.
I'm going to cherish every moment and do my best from now on.
Now, let's start with this app-cam.
JuiceJuice Tokyo Blur Making of the music video shooting Making of JuiceJuice Tokyo Blur Music Video Shooting
Released on May 15, Tokyo Blur
From JuiceJuice's latest single
Please take a look at the making of the music video for "Tokyo Blur" from JuiceJuice's latest single!
Good morning.
Please roll the camera.
It's rolling!
Okay.
I love you. I don't love you.
It's night in the city.
I don't love you. I love you.
It's getting a little bit crazy in here.
There are two sets of dancers, this one and a silver set with glittering lights,
There are also some light and dark versions of the dance shots,
I look forward to seeing the replays.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching.
I was told that it looks stylish, so I will do my best to make it look stylish.
Thank you for watching.
mv The shooting is going well, but this time the main color is green, and the studio set is green and white, and the costumes are also green and white.
It's been quite a while since I've danced in costumes made for a music video like this, so each costume has its own unique shape and color.
I like the way the shapes and personalities of the costumes are expressed in the music video, and I'm not sure what the music video will actually look like, but I'm sure it will be stylish.
I don't know what the music video will actually look like yet, but I'm sure it will be very stylish.
Thank you for watching!
Kizuna ni naru toki naru lie
Graduation It wasn't you.
That's all there is to it.
Temptation Shouki no Love & Joy
Untie me
The hand that takes away the sleepless love
Leave the Passenger Seat
Let's go see a new morning
Graduation, gently by the back of my hair
With a hunch of why
5.6.7.8
Brand new, brand new, new lifeBrand new, brand new, new life
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't love you, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
I don't even touch your hand, it's raining hot
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Boo-boo!
Tense faction, love end of the outfit, leave me smiling
World hands, sleepless love, leave my seat
New me, new morning I see
Gradillation, why are you looking at me with your hair back?
Why are you looking at me, why are you looking at me, why are you looking at me, why are you looking at me
me
We're shooting a dance scene right now.
It's called Tokyo Blur, just like Juice Chus.
I think you will enjoy the urban sound and dance!
Why is it that I can't leave your fon alone, you're so weak
Silence for peace, no escape, breath stopping breathing
Temptation Love end eye in profile
Someday I'm piling up
Kindness to pass it on to each other, faded things.
K.O.!
Kizuna ni naru naru kizuna ni naru lie
Graduation It wasn't you
That's all there is to it.
We just finished shooting the music video for Tokyo Brown!
Look at this set!
Well, it's been quite a while since I've shot a music video with a set, so I was really happy about that, but above all, this was Akari Uemura's last music video shoot, so how was it?
Oh, OK!
How was I?
How did you like it? I think it turned out great.
I think it looked great!
And the squid-like outfit.
Squid!
Oh, squid!
I'm a little disappointed that we don't have an octopus, but what can I say? I hope you enjoy the show!
Enjoy the show! Best regards!
How was it?
I watched the making of Tokyo Brown's music video shoot.
I saw the making of the shooting of the music video for "Tokyo Brown", and I thought it was really great that everyone was smiling all the time.
I thought it was wonderful that everyone was smiling all the time during the shoot.
They all have their own personalities.
They looked very mature during the music video shooting.
They were using their fingers so beautifully, but when it came to the making of the music video
But when it comes to the making of the music video, you can see them being very friendly.
It's something that can only be done here, and I really enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
How was the shooting?
Yes, it was.
When we were shooting the music video, the costumes were the same.
The set also had Mr. Kamimura's color.
Yes, in various places.
Even the accessories had Mr. Uemura's colors in them.
I was thinking about how I was going to end up with Mr. Uemura there as well.
I could really feel the atmosphere that Mr. Uemura created.
Yes.
I really like it because it's friendly and relaxing.
Also, the first time I saw the lyrics of Tokyo Mura, I thought they sounded like juice juice.
I don't know how to describe the tone of the song.
Before the chorus, there are about 3 chord changes.
The key changes about 3 steps before the chorus, and the emotion changes a lot.
It's like a shaking feeling.
It's like it's shaking me.
I love the music and the lyrics to the music.
I'm so happy that I'll be able to listen to this wonderful song at live performances.
Thank you very much!
That's all for the making of the Juice Tokyo Bra music video shoot!
Temptation: Love Enjoy!
Here, keep changing it
Take away the handle Sleepless eyes
juice juice news india
Tokyo Brown Love On Site
It's been a while. Thanks for watching.
And here we go.And here's the next one.
Biophonic 2 Making Video
Biophonic was born from the fusion of BEYONES and SYMPHONIC
The Biophonic 2 was held in Tokyo and Kobe.
This time, we will show you the rehearsal and the behind-the-scenes of the Tokyo performance.
Please have a look!
Here you go!
Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
I'll be doing a talk box this time.
We're preparing for it.
Last time, yes, we didn't have one.
And after that last time
Ikuro Fujiwara came to see our concert.
He saw the talkbox and said, "Let's do it next time!
He saw the talkbox and said, "Let's do it for sure!
That's how it came to be.
I am so happy!
My beauty is from the front
From the front
They all have the exact same dress shape!
It's quite unusual.
A belt with a slightly different design.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Some are thick, some are thin.
Two.
That's not a chord.
I got two chords.
Oh, really?
We're currently rehearsing for the spring tour
And myophonic rehearsals at the same time.
Our heads are in a whirl.
Glad to hear it.
This is Mion!
Best regards!
I am really looking forward to making great music and creating a great stage with you again!
We will do our best to deliver a great performance to as many people as possible, so please give us your support! We will do our best to deliver a great performance to many people, so please give us your support!
We are going to perform tomorrow!
Today is the first time for me to meet the orchestra, and it's been a year since I've seen them,
Today is the most important day, so I hope we can rehearse carefully today and have fun tomorrow!
I will do my best!
A new song called "Japanese DNA
Mr. Mikuro wrote the melody for SHORKY, and we are going to perform it with twinging SHORKY this time.
We will perform with twinging SHORKY this time!
I will do my best!
Cute!
This is also one by one
Yes
It's amazing.
Cute.
So elaborate.
I have a necklace.
I have a choker.
It's adorable.
Now I'm going to add a head, so I'm even more excited for the show!
Thank you very much for watching.
Today is the day of the show!
Euphonic 2
It's been a year since I've been to this venue.
It's different from the concert hall where we usually stand.
The sound is totally different just by talking.
Above all, the audience is on the side of the stage.
There are seats on the stage side.
It's right there.
I also thought it's like an orchestra or something.
I'm so nervous, I have goosebumps.
Euphnique 2
It's hard to play bytes.
I'm finally pushed by the sound.
It's so different from the usual live performance
It's totally different from the usual live performance.
I'm nervous.I do get nervous.
Euphnique 2
First concert venue in two years
My voice, my heart, my soul, my screams, everything, I'm going to fight.
Well, I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I hope you have a good time.
Let's go beyond
beyond
Nasu
Thank you very much
The performance of Miohonic 2 is over!
It was a lot of fun!
This is the second time for me.
I loved the world view and space of Miohonic so much.
I have been looking forward to today's performance for a long time.
I've been looking forward to this day's performance, but the best part is that we are going to perform with the orchestra's live video.
I've been looking forward to today's performance for a long time.
I was really looking forward to today's performance, but the best part of it was that we could see a lot of
I think the highlight of the show is that you can see a lot of ions that you can only see in this performance.
Also, there is a section in the middle of the show where we are allowed to perform a ceremony.
I had a chance to do it.
It's an experience that you can only have here.
I chewed and shook the ceremony with all my might.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, sir.
I've seen the making of MIOHONIC 2.
I watched the making of the video.
Yes, it's a collaboration with an orchestra, isn't it?
My favorite thing about the orchestra is...
First of all, I love the sound of tuning during the preparation stage.
There's so much music playing.
I've been playing the violin since I was a little girl.I've been playing the violin since I was a little kid.
I used to play in the orchestra.
It reminded me of the old days.
I was a little bit moved by it.
It's amazing that you can see it from that point of view.
The sound and your performance, and the way you played the harp, the piano, and the talk box.
and the Beyonce's act, and the chorus, and the piano, and the talk box...
I'm sure the audience will be so happy when they leave.
I felt so happy thinking that I would go home with a full stomach.
I really enjoyed the making of the video, didn't I?
Just watching the making of the video made me feel happy.
I was excited and wished I could have been there to see it.
I could really feel that special feeling.
Just looking at it, I wanted to shake it together with them.
I also felt like shaking the floor with them, and the thickness of the sound must be different, so I was very excited and thrilled to be a part of the making of this video.
That's all for the making of Biophonic 2.
Are you enjoying it? Please watch the rest of the video!
Next up is the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30th and 31st.
We'll be focusing on the solos and shuffle units.
Slow down, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Chan chan chan chan chan chan chan chan!
Let's do it.
I just had my wisdom teeth removed. I can't open my mouth.
I'm not very good at singing.
I'm sorry. You should see me in the show.
You've got a great voice.
Nanjing, tego, Calediiesta.
See you soon.
See you.
I had a feeling it was going to hit 9:00.
I was already wondering what kind of shuffle it would be before I even turned the page.
I opened it like a solo, or a unit, or a group of people.
I wasn't that wowed.
This is my first solo performance.
I don't think I'll have a chance to sing solo on a big stage.
I'm sure I'll be nervous.
But I was happy. But I was happy.
I tried to choose a song that would fit the feel of my song.
But I missed a lot.
And to play a cute song...
It's like a gap.
I thought it would be a big surprise to see you like that.
I thought about that for a while.
But after all, I can only sing one song.
So I thought it would be nice to sing a song that really brings out my voice.
I really like this song by Cute.
And when I was with the band, I was watching from the side.
I thought it was really cool.
I want to do my best to make my solo cool.
I'm doing it with all of you, right?
So I think I'm good here.
I've always believed in it.
I know
Oh, I know!
One by one
two people two people one person
This is the second time I've won a prize.
I had previously performed as a duo with Yuhane Yamazaki at Finafest.
I can't forget the memories and impressions of that time, the nervousness and excitement I felt when we got on stage.
I can't forget the memories of that time and the feeling of excitement when we were on stage.
I was really nervous this time, too.
Even though we've only performed together a few times, I can still taste the thrill of delivering the song to you.
I'm looking forward to the experience, but at the same time, I'm nervous at the same time.
But I'm happy that I'm going to win, so I'm going to do my best.But I was still happy to win, so I decided to do my best.
This is the first time I, Yonemura, have won a prize.
That's right, when I was watching the trio for the first time.
I finally won.
I thought I had won.
But this time, I'm going to perform with Shiori Nishida and Hiramiya-san, so it's going to be a kind of cool trio.
I thought it was going to be a kind of cool trio.
I'm really looking forward to it.
We just had a rehearsal.
I'm really looking forward to the performance.
I'm really looking forward to it!
This is my third time, but it's been four years.
The previous two times were solo performances, so this kind of shuffle is a new experience for me,
I can complete many parts of a solo performance in my own way,
I wasn't worried about the amount of practice or anything like that, but the group was different and the time was limited,
But, you know, you only have one chance to practice, so you want to make it the best one.
Well, we will have one more practice session with all three of us, but it will be today,
We will all improve our skills and bring them to the show.
I will do my best!
I'm not too nervous right now.
But I'm sure I would be if it was right before the show.
But today we have a juice block before the solo.
So I'm going to get up and get ready for the solo.
I'm going to prepare for it.
Shiori Ishida and Kirara Yonemura are going to play as a trio this time.
We're going to perform a song called "sexy natural body".
It's quite a difficult song for the three of us to perform.
Ms. Ishida gave us a lot of advice.
I'm going to do my best to deliver a passionate performance
I will do my best to deliver a passionate performance.
When Yonemura-san and Miyon Hirai were rehearsing
I was really impressed by their aura.
I thought their faces were really cool.
I want to do my best so that the three of us can create something as good as them.
I want to do my best too.
I've practiced a lot, but I'm still a little nervous.
But in the show, I'm going to play the role of a strong woman calmly.
Now that our block of the premiere is over, I'm really looking forward to the show.We've just finished our block of premiums and we're sweating.
I'm sweating and sweating.
I'm going to change my mind a little bit.
I'm going to do my best to be sexy and feminine.
I'm nervous, but I'll do my best.
I can't wait to see you.
I want to meet you.
I want to see you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I want you to hold me forever.
What is it?
I loved you so much and I'm saying goodbye.
Thank you for watching.
I wasn't too nervous. It was fun. It was crazy.
I don't remember much.
I feel like I enjoyed it.
It's not every day you get to see an orange view all over a big venue.
I'm glad you all had a great time.
Thank you so much.
Yay! It's over!
Thank you very much.
I was pretty panicky during the rehearsal, but
I was pretty panicky during rehearsals, but I was able to calm down during the performance.
Not more calm than in rehearsal, but I was able to focus on getting into the world.
I'm glad that I was able to focus on getting into the world.
You were excited at the beginning.
Early on.
The songs were a little bit fun.
Thank you very much.
Ishiori was wonderful.
It was fun.
I think we practiced a lot, and the audience's reaction was great.
The audience's reaction was great.
I'm really glad we chose this song.
It was a lot of fun.It was fun.
I saw the video of Kinafest and it really looked great from the rehearsal.
It was really great from the rehearsal.
The performance was really cool, too.
I could feel that you were concentrating on the performance from the rehearsal, and I was very happy to hear the reason for the song selection.
I'm very happy to hear the reason for the song selection.
During the show, I often see Tsubaki Factory from the side of the stage, and I'm always saying, "I like it here, I like it here, I like it here.
I tend to watch them while saying "this one's good, this one's good, this one's good.
But this time, we were all silent.
I got goosebumps.
It was such a wonderful shuffle unit that gave me goosebumps.
I'd have to say Lisawar.
It was the first time for me to win a prize at Hinafest, and I was so excited to see the shuffle.
That's right.
That's why I was getting nervous.
I remember how I was nervous while watching the show.
I remembered a lot of things.
The three shuffle performers each had their own colorful differences.
I thought that the three of you have some kind of hidden passion inside.
And the color of Ms. Danbara's tears was so beautiful.
The color of Mr. Danbara's tears
For example, Mr. Danbara sang in Italian and said, "I don't know Italian, but I can sing in Italian.
We don't know Italian.
but I think the lyrics are conveyed through the melody.
I really wanted to learn from the expression that conveyed the content of the lyrics.
It was so beautiful!
Thank you very much.
That's all for the making of Hello Project Hinafes 2024!
Thank you for all your hard work!
It's time for Saori Onoda and Kazuka Arisawa to say goodbye to Apkami!
We've seen a lot of videos this time, but I, Arisawa, would like to start with the Tokyo Bras.
I, Arisawa, would like to start with a behind-the-scenes look at the shooting of the music video for "Tokyo Bras".
It was a little embarrassing to see my own making-of video.
But I was a little embarrassed to see my own making-of video.
I could see how it looks like on camera.
I hadn't seen the other members' shots.
I was very happy to see it in this making-of video.
The most memorable moment for me was Danbara-san's solo at the Hina festival. I was most impressed by Danbara-san's solo at the Hina Fest.
I was able to see the performance.
even during the rehearsal.
I had goosebumps all over my body
I had goosebumps all over my body.
She said she had her wisdom teeth removed.
I couldn't tell at all.
I thought that was a cute gap between the two of us.
I thought, "I'm in the same group with a great senior.
I thought to myself, "I'm in the same group with an amazing senior, so I'm going to steal what I can from him.
I had goosebumps because of all the wonderful images.
I had goosebumps. I, Onoda, was really moved by the biophonic 2. I really wanted to do a live performance with this orchestra.
There was a sense of direction that only BEYOND can bring out, and there were some songs and choruses.
Tsubaki Factory had a live band performance for their major debut anniversary event,
I also had a live band performance for Tsubaki Factory's major debut anniversary event, which has become a regular event for us,
I would like to do my best to challenge more things in the future.
In "up-cami", we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we will introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see.
This time, upcami is with Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory,
and JuiceJuice's Arisawa Ichika.
Goodbye!
In the next episode of Upokami, we will be talking about JuiceJuice's Love for Nothing! music video making-of, and,
Tsubaki Factory Power Flower: Now is the time to be an eye! and the recording of "Tsubaki Factory Power Flower: Now is the time to be an eye.
Please look forward to it!
Now is the time to unite, unite our feelings and move forward, to a place we've never seen before.